ragesw.com 2005-12-17

# Rage Software Privacy Policy

**General**

Rage Software respects the privacy of every individual who visits our web site.

  * Rage Software will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (ie. your name, address, or email address) unless you provide it voluntarily.
  * Rage Software will not give, trade, sell, or otherwise distribute the personal information you provide us with.
  * Rage Software will often provide links to web sites that our out of our control, but that we feel are appropriate for viewers. Rage Software is not responsible for the content or privacy policy of the Web sites we may link to.

**Information that we collect**

When you visit ragesw.com, we collect basic information that does not identify individual users. The information that we collect includes which pages are visited, the page that refereed you to our site and some information about your browser and OS type.

We do not collect personal information such as email, name, address, etc... unless you voluntarily submit it to us. When you purchase our software only the fields that you fill out are sent to us.

 **Surveys and Other Online Forms**

To help us make both our services and software better, we ask that you fill out our Online Survey so that we know what you want and can serve you better.

By filling out our survey you allow us to use any information that is submitted along with your name on our web site. We will not, however, use your email or any other personal information on our web site or in our products.

 **How we use information**

The information that we collect helps us make our web site better, get you your serial numbers for our products and send you reply emails to your questions and comments.

When you submit a question via our online form, your email address allows us to reply to you and answer your queries. We will never sell, or give your email address to any third party organizations

 **Access or Change your information**

If you would like to access the personally identifiable information we have maintained about you, just send us an email along with your name and serial number and we will send you your details. This does not apply to your Credit Card number since we never see this information or store it in anyway.

If you would like us to change or correct errors in the details we currently have, you can send us a request that credibly shows error

 **Shopping on RageSW.com**

Ordering our products is completely safe. You never have to worry about Credit Card safety when ordering our products.

Rage Software uses the services of eSellerate to handle payments. eSellerate is a well respected company which has been offering many years of safe and efficient methods of ordering products online. Your credit card information can not be read as it travels to our ordering system. eSellerate maintains their own security and privacy polices. You can visit the eSellerate web site [here](http://www.esellerate.net/) for more information

All information you enter in the eSellerate.net order form will be shared with Rage Software in order to send you your serial number for the product you purchased. This does not apply for your credit card information. We never get your credit card number.

 **Public Forums, Chats etc...**

Rage Software may make public forums, chat rooms or newgroups available to its visitors. Rage Software can not be held responsible for the content or information on these public forums. Any information that is disclosed will become available to the public and anyone who visits the Rage Software web site. Please use caution when posting personal information.

 **Further Information**

Rage Software is dedicated to providing you with an easy and safe way to purchase our products. We also respect your privacy and will never release the information that we collect to third party organizations. For more information please contact us
